Allen Collegiate Center; Records ua442
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Transfer Policy, 1973 (Box 4 (Allen Collegiate Center Records ), Folder 26)
- Undergraduate Bulletin Copy, Undated (Box 4 (Allen Collegiate Center Records ), Folder 27)
- Undergraduate Office, 1970-1971 (Box 4 (Allen Collegiate Center Records ), Folder 28)
- University College, 1973-1974 (Box 4 (Allen Collegiate Center Records ), Folder 29)
- Uptown Equivalencies, Undated (Box 4 (Allen Collegiate Center Records ), Folder 30)
- U.S. Office of Education, 1971-1973; Undated (Box 4 (Allen Collegiate Center Records ), Folder 31)
- Waiver of Major Requirements, Undated (Box 4 (Allen Collegiate Center Records ), Folder 32)
- Women and Social Change, 1975; Undated (Box 4 (Allen Collegiate Center Records ), Folder 33)